本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子 字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第1季第3集
S01E03 Picture Perfect
早上好 我的毛茸茸的小朋友
Good morning,my little furry friend.
早上好 有什么可以效劳的吗?
Morning.Can I help you?
早上好 我们是西伦敦卫生部的.
Morning.West London Dept.Of Sanitation.
你们大概知道啮齿动物在这个街区横行的事情吧?
You're probably aware of the rodent infestation along this block?
- 你到底想说什么? - 老鼠
- What are you talking about? - Rats.
老鼠做事很谨慎
They can be discreet.
它们会损坏你的库存以及传播肮脏的疾病
But they can damage your stock as well as spreading nasty diseases.
我们这儿没有老鼠 请让我看看你们的证件
We don't have any rats!Let me see some ID,please.
(通常为灭虫或消毒杀菌而熏烟)
我们会熏蒸到大约12点 在这之前不能进来
We'll be fumigating till about 12:00.I'd keep out of the way till then.
还有,这事情你们自己知道就可以了
And keep this to yourselves.
当关系到生意的声誉的时候 你最好三思而行
Discretion is always the best policy where business reputations are concerned.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的 她很快就来
All right,she'll be here any minute.
- 扮的稀罕点 - 是的
- Better make yourself scarce. - Yeah.
- 早上好 Gates小姐 - 早上好
- Good morning,Miss Gates. - Morning.
- 是这儿吗? - 是的
- Is this it,then? - Yeah.
请进
Come in.
我直接说重点吧,Pomeroy先生
I'll come right to the point,Mr.Pomeroy.
你是个投机者 一个不错的投机者
You're a chancer.A beautiful chancer.
但你还只是个家具搬运商
But nevertheless,you're a furniture mover.
你对于杰出的艺术可能知道多少?
What could you possibly know about fine art?
你真的准备出500,000买这个吗?
Are you really going to pay 500,000 for it?
是的
Yes,I am.
好吧 我不准备
Okay,no,I'm not.
我的最高只能出到250,000镑
My ceiling's actually 250,000...
但是我在寻找一个适合我的合伙人
but I'm looking for a partner who can match me.
你知道 如果这是真的,它会值几百万
You know,if this is genuine,it could be worth several million.
对此我没有怀疑
I don't doubt that.
好的 我们一起去我的画廊看看这画
Right.So,we will view the painting at my gallery together.
如果我感到满意 我会考虑和你五五分成
If I am satisfied,then I will consider going 50-50 with you.
Gates小姐 你真是太慷慨了
That's incredibly generous,Miss Gates.
我警告你 我听取有信服力的
I do warn you,I take some convincing.
再见
Bye.
哦,太棒了,她上钩了
Yes,we're on.
不 我还在进入Berlgravia中
No,I'm staying put in Belgravia.
护士 看在老天的份上 弄掉它
Nurse,for the love of God,get rid of this!
难以置信
Unbelievable.
- 那女人从不闭嘴吗? - 告诉我
- Does that woman ever shut up? - Tell me about it.
Ernie 你有什么?
What you got,Ernie?
- 不多 - 那是什么?没什么
- Not much. - What's that?Nothing.
三张相同和二张相同的牌 胜者拿走全部
Full house.Winner takes all,mate.
听者 你或许想好好考虑注意下你的肯定
Listen.You might want to consider watching that tell of yours.
但肯定会稍稍泄漏你的牌 让我知道你在想什么
A tell is a little giveaway sign.Lets me know what you're thinking.
就像当你有个好帮手之后 你开始鼓掌
Like when you've got a good hand,you start clapping...
然后开始大笑 想想吧
and roaring with laughter.Think about it.
- 再见 - 祝你好运
- See you. - Good luck.
护士!
Nurse!
我不在乎他认为价值多少 就100,000不能再多
I don't care what he thinks it's worth,go to 100,000 and no more.
好的 我走过去 派辆车接我
Right,I'm taking a walk.Send the car for me.
这是...
Is that...
Rachel的律师,她要财产转让
Rachel's lawyer.She wants a settlement.
- 要多少? - 我想就在这个信封里面
- How much? - I guess that's in the envelope.
准备付吗?
Gonna pay?
别催我 我还没决定打开它
Don't rush me.I haven't even decided to open it yet.
快点 怎么了?
Come on,what's the matter?
我不知道
I don't know.
我感觉有些不对
Something just doesn't feel right.
Mickey 外面有个人在找我们 我和Ash
Mickey,there's a man outside looking for us.Me and Ash.
但是他是Harry我是Gordon
Except he's Harry and I'm Gordon.
- 他进来的时候告诉他们我死了 - 我正在中国
- When he comes in here,tell him I'm dead. - And I'm in China.
瞧,我不知道你在说什么,伙计
Look,I don't know who you're talking about,mate.
- 你想让我相信吗? - 对不起
- Do you expect me to believe that? - I'm sorry.
打搅,你在找Harry和Gordon吗
Excuse me.You're looking for Harry and Gordon.
我知道我来对了地方 我觉得你该告诉我一声
I knew I had the right place.I think I deserve a word with them.
对不起 但是他们
I'm sorry,but they're...
别告诉我 在国外
Don't tell me.Out of the country.
Marrakesh 经营贸易
Marrakesh.For the trade fair.
好 当他们回来的时候 告诉他们"做得不错"
Well,when they get back,tell them "well done" from me.
他们对我做得不错 非常聪明
They did me good.Very clever.
如果他们想知道自己曾经有多聪明 这是我的名片
If they want to see how clever they've been,here's my card.
这是你还被关在里面发生的事情
It was while you were inside.
是啊,我们厌倦了小鱼小虾
Yeah,we was bored of the small fish.
我们从这儿打个电话 一个电话
We made one call from here.One ruddy call.
而Naveen会得到一个详细记录的电话账单 然后他会追踪你
And Naveen gets an itemized phone bill and he traces you.
伙计们 这就是第一步
That's Chapter One,boys.
不 听起来不错 Mickey 是贸易,但是国际性的
No,it was sweet,Mickey.The rag trade,but international.
角色,剧本,让整个事情慢慢发展起来
The Rolex,the Jag.Worked the whole thing up.
我看上去像洛克菲勒
I looked like Rockefeller.
我设了个套,Naveen
I roped in the mark,Naveen.
有一个T恤的工厂
Has a T-shirt factory.
- 你真的那么做了? - 是的
- You did that? - Yeah.
我们计划20,000,但是他想要投入50,000
We planned on 20,000,but he wanted in for 50,000.
如果我们知道他有麻烦,就不会去弄他了
If we'd known he was in trouble,we would have left him alone.
但是他搞得像个大人物
But he was acting the big man.
你从一个绝望的人手中骗走了钱
You took money from a desperate man.
这是我们做的吗?Muggers?
Is that what we are?Muggers?
我们以为他起码能满足温饱
We thought he could afford to be fleeced.
我们用美好的承诺麻醉了他
We ripped him off in good faith.
这解释了不少我这两天的感受
This explains a lot of what I've been feeling recently.
我觉得我们最近很倒霉
I think we're under a jinx.
拜托
Come on.
Ash 我们为什么需要规定?
Why do we have codes,Ash?
因为这是一件有分寸的事情
Because it's a decent thing.
不 诈骗根本不是一件有分寸的事情
No,the decent thing is not to grift at all.
我们有规定,因为坏举动会带来坏运气
And we have a code because bad behavior makes bad luck.
这没有倒霉的事情,伙计
There's no jinx,mate.
切牌
Cut.
也许我们确实下错了套
Maybe we did pick the wrong mark.
但是 Mickey 再一次成为局内人我感觉很好
But it felt so good to be the inside man again,Mickey.
你知道,去感觉那种激情
You know,to feel that glow.
破产者,你几乎已经可以嗅出来了
Receivers.You can practically smell them.
Rachel说我把她的一生拖下了水
Rachel says I dragged her life into the gutter.
我不认为这样
I don't see it that way.
但是从一个绝望的人手中拿走他的最后一便士
But taking a desperate man for his last penny.
你总是说我们必须依靠自己的决定生活
You always say we have to live by our decision.
那你能靠这个人生活吗?
And can you live with this one?
一个包,没别的了
One bag.And that's that.
没什么 我是这个雕刻家的朋友
It's all right,I'm a friend of the sculptor's.
噢 真是令人印象深刻
Yeah.Impressive piece.
在那儿水滴如此令人印象深刻
Impressive use of the blobs there.
我在想是什么让他这么做
I wonder what compelled him.
我觉得如果你看过这艺术家早期的作品
I think if you look at the artist's earlier works...
这个答案会显而易见
it becomes obvious.
早期的作品?这个是他唯一的作品
Earlier work?This is the only one.
他19岁就死了
He was 19 when he died.
我更多的是在想他儿童时期的素材
I was thinking more of his childhood stuff.
你知道 小时候他用粉笔画的一些东西
You know,some of his early pieces that he did in crayon.
搞笑
Teasing.
它值多少钱?20,000镑 不管怎么样我会考虑一下的
What's it worth?20,000.I'll think about it anyway.
Gates画廊一般都需要预约才能来参观的
Of course,the Gates Gallery is usually viewed by appointment.
- 你是她内部圈子的人吗? - 不是
- Are you one of her inner circle? - No.
我只是认为艺术是给大家看的
I just think that art is for everyone.
大家不包括穷人和一般买家...
Not when everyone includes all the poor struggling dealers and buyers...
- 不然她靠什么宰人 - 说的多真实啊
- that she's ripped off over the years. - How true.
Meredith Gates喜欢和人保持一定的距离
Meredith Gates likes to keep mere mortals at a safe distance.
Dali的作品被认为以夸张的价格满足了空虚古怪的人
Dali's sketches go for inflated prices to satisfy vanity-driven eccentrics...
却没于真正的艺术评价
with no real art appreciation.
至少在我付给他三分之一真正价值的时候这么说的
At least that's what I told him before I paid him a third of their real value.
我一直想写一篇关于她的文章 也许开一个博览会?
I've been hoping to write an article on her,maybe even an expos?
看看她
Just look at her.
她向大众展示的唯一原因
The only reason she's opened to the proles...
就是她想最大限度的公开她的新蒙德里安画风
is because she wants maximum publicity for her new Mondrians.
- 天啊 你不是她的朋友吧? - 不是
- God,you're not a friend of hers,are you? - No.
我也是一个蒙德里安的追随者
I am after a Mondrian myself.
他们正在展出
They're just for show.
Bea Watson 艺术记者
Bea Watson,art journalist.
Daniel Pomeroy 收藏家
Daniel Pomeroy,collector.
你真的是蒙德里安的追随者吗?
You're not really after a Mondrian,are you?
我是说,Meredith会杀了其他人
I mean,Meredith would kill for another one.
中间的那幅画她花了250000买的
That piece in the middle she bought for 250,000.
是的,这就是Piet Mondrian
Right.This is Piet Mondrian.
1872年 生于荷兰
Born in Holland,1872.
这里有一些他的油画
These are a few of his paintings.
很不错,但他们不会让你胡说的
Quite nice,but they don't blow your bollocks off.
突然 在1909年
Suddenly in 1909...
嬉皮士成了主流
in comes the hippy shit.
几年之后 看这个
Few years later,this.
注意从后面看这个 这就是我们的利益
Pay attention at the back.This is for your benefit.
大多数人猜想在看了毕加索的展览之后
Most people reckon that Mondrian got all fired up...
蒙德里安整个人勃然大怒...
after seeing an exhibition by Picasso...
他开始对那个让人产生幻觉的树 发表滔滔不绝的评论
and that's when he started boshing out the psychedelic trees.
但是 这里面有一个秘密
But there's a mystery involved.
有些人声称Mondrian在玩抽象派
Some claim that Mondrian was playing around with abstract art...
甚至早在毕加索之前
before Picasso even had a sniff.
因为他是一个不会装腔作势的小子
But because he was such an unassuming bloke...
他自己保留着那些作品
he kept it to himself...
直到毕加索之后才公众于世
and only went public after Picasso.
你们知道这意味着什么吗?
And do we know what that would mean,class?
蒙德里安可能发明了一种新的艺术
Mondrian could've invented a new type of art...
但是毕加索拿走了他所有的荣誉
but Picasso took all the glory.
你答得不错
Give that man an A-plus.
好吧,你去过一个艺术画廊也读了些书
All right,so you've been to an art gallery and read a book.
但是这跟些有什么关系呢?
What's all this got to do with six figures?
很好 假设这个秘密已经解决了
Well,suppose the mystery was solved.
假设一幅画被发现 然后绘画的日期是1902或者1903
Supposing a painting was discovered that was dated,say,1902 or 1903...
- 在毕加索发明... - 立体派
- before Picasso invented... - Cubism.
在毕加索发明立体派之前
Before Picasso invented Cubism.
说这个画是蒙德里安的...
And say this painting was a Mondrian...
它会改变艺术史
it would turn art history on its head.
确切的说 这就像我们给他们 蒙娜丽莎一样
Exactly.And it's not like we gotta give them the Mona Lisa.
我们有目标了 知道吗?Meredith Gates
We've got the mark,okay?Meredith Gates.
我们诱饵也有了 蒙德里安
We've got the bait:Mondrian.
我们仿造一幅画 然后告诉她...
We fake the right painting,and all we gotta tell her...
要有多少个零写在她的支票上
is how many noughts to put on the check.
我们出去走下
Let's take a walk.
你听说过以伊卡洛斯吗?
Have you heard of Icarus?
当然了,邦德的反派,对吧?
'Course I have.He's a Bond villain,ain't he?
伊卡洛斯朝太阳飞的太近了然后被烧着了
Icarus flew too close to the sun and got burnt.
很好 Mickey 像我这样的人不会引火烧身的
Well,Mickey,guys like me don't get burnt.
我们只会被晒黑
We get tanned.
如果我们倒霉呢?
And what if we're jinxed?
你是说骗子的倒霉吗?
You talking about the grifter's jinx?
Albert被强盗报答,然后你又赚到了一个子弹
Albert getting strapped by that gangster,then you picking up an extra bullet.
你知道 我们不是会计师 是吧?
You know,we're not accountants,are we?
这只是该死巧合
Shit happens.
不 这是个坏的预兆 我可以感觉到 它正在我们的头上
No,it's a bad vibe.I can feel it,and it's right on our heads.
我以前告诉过你,伙计 Lara Croft从来不会答复
I've told you before,boys,Lara Croft is never gonna reply.
不 这是一个为艺术商人和古董商的交易网站
No,this is a website for art dealers and antique buffs to swap stories.
我正在用E-mail和我自己会谈
I'm running an e-mail conversation with meself.
在荷兰
In Dutch.
那么你那两个虚构的荷兰人在谈论什么?
So what are your two fictional Dutchmen talking about?
Mikcey 说过不要
Mickey said no.
我知道 我们有两个艺术商人在谈论这个新画
I know.We got two art dealers gossiping about this new painting.
一个人对另外一个人说 "留着它对你有好处"
One guy says to the other one,"Keep this to yourself."
那么如果它不能引起点波澜 什么都不是呢?
Now if that don't create a buzz,nothing will,will it?
你想把Meredith Gates引到这里来?
So you wanna draw Meredith Gates into this?
如果说有神秘的蒙德里安的新作 传到她的耳中
If word gets to her that there's this mysterious new Mondrian out there...
就对我们有利了
then suddenly it'll be a lot better for us.
他们以为有人在背后操纵的线索是很模糊的
Marks are so much softer when they think they're the ones doing the running.
你认为这样会说服Mikcey也参与吗?
And you think this will persuade Mickey to go along with it?
根本没有什么坏运气
There's no jinx.
当我们把它完成后他会发现的
When we pull this one off he'll see that.
他需要被说服
He'll need a lot of persuading.
我知道他会的
I know he will.
这就是我为什么在做这件事
That's why I'm working on it.
Hook先生
Mr.Hook.
- 不好意思 让你久等了 - 没关系
- Sorry to keep you waiting. - Not at all.
这个一定就是...
And this must be...
Jeremiah Hook.Bea Watson 艺术专栏记者
Jeremiah Hook.Bea Watson,art journalist.
Hook先生,我也不知道我为什么到这里
I'm not entirely sure why I'm here,Mr.Hook.
不要告诉我你来这里是一个错误
Don't tell me you're here under false pretenses.
- 酒来了 我随便喝了 - 当然
- There you go.I took the liberty. - Yes,you did.
我不能久留
I can't stay long.
我还有个作品要交给 艺术世界 杂志 我不能让编辑焦虑
I've got a piece to deliver to Art World magazine and I can't upset the editor.
好的 让我们开门见山吧
Okay,let's cut straight to the chase.
Hook先生是一个国际古董商人
Mr.Hook is an international antiques dealer.
他最近得到了一小幅油画
He's recently come into possession of a small oil.
什么种类的油画?
What sort of oil?
署名是P.蒙德里安 日期是1902年
Well,it was signed by Piet Mondrian,dated 1902.
它在英特网上关于这个作品有些言论
There's a buzz about a new work on the Internet.
我能看看吗?
Can I see it?
你把它带过来了吗?
Do you have it here in town?
Bea 你能为我们做的就是鉴别它
What you could do for us,Bea,is authenticate it.
我们将给你独家的报道作为回报
And in return I'd give you exclusive rights.
为了什么?
To what?
我可能要买这幅画
I may buy this painting.
它虽然不大但是极富意义
It is small but it is significant.
我的确能引起一些艺术出版商的兴趣
I certainly could interest a few gallery publications.
抱歉 我不会去描述早期的蒙德里安
But I'm sorry,I wouldn't describe an early Mondrian...
以及它对全世界的意义
as all that significant to the wider world.
我必须走了
I have to go.
我也是 把我们这次谈话忘记吧
So do I.Forget we had this meeting.
没什么事情了 抱歉浪费你宝贵的时间了
There's no story here.I'm sorry to have wasted your time.
你什么意思?这里面没有文章?
What do you mean,there's no story here?
- 就这样 - 事实上...
- Just that. - Actually...
- 这里有文章 - 事实上 根本没有
- there is a story. - Actually,there isn't a story.
它要远远超出一个正常油画的意义 是不是?
It's more than just a regular landscape,isn't it?
当然不是 1902年?不
Of course not.1902?No.
好吧 Hook先生
All right,Mr.Hook.
如果你改变了主意
If you change your mind...
对不起 我必须走了
Sorry.I really have to go.
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye-bye.
你好
Hello.
你怎么知道我会出现?
How did you know I'd turn up?
因为留下了线索
Because I scented the invite.
你真的撇下这个计划离开吗?
Did you have to go and gut the whole plan like a kipper?
你难道没有意识到刚才发生的事情吗?
Did you not just see what happened there?
服务员
Waiter.
在她认为我不感兴趣之前她不会感兴趣的
She wasn't interested until she thought that I wasn't interested.
现在 她有兴趣了
Now she's intrigued.
对不起 我们不能喝这个,它发酸了
Sorry,we can't drink this.It's sour.
记住 Tip Jones是业界最好的伪造者
Remember,Tip Jones is the best forger in the business...
但是我不会相信他的
but I trust him about as far as I can throw a horsebox.
他在玩心理游戏 他会让你徒劳无获
He plays mind games.He'll have you chasing your own tail.
他总想办法骗你
He's got a brain like a steel trap.
好了
There we go.
你听说过人们对麻醉剂的反映总是这么糟糕,是吧?
Well,you hear about people reacting badly to anesthetic,don't you?
疝气
Hernia op.
真是悲惨
Bloody tragic.
我是Mickey Stone
I'm Mickey Stone.
- 我们走吧 - 等下
- We're out of here. - Wait.
干什么?
What for?
如果我们再呆一会儿的话 他会开始唱"我是个小茶壶..."
If we stay any longer,he's gonna sing I'm a Little Teapot...
然后他会挥动他的手
and he's gonna poop in his hand.
Tip 表演结束了
The show is over,Tip.
我们要做笔大买卖
We're here on serious business.
如果你做得好的话 你会得到10万镑
If you do this job right,you're in for 100,000.
停止玩这恶心的游戏
So stop playing silly buggers.
15万,要不就走人
150,000.Take it or leave it.
这个是维纳斯的
...belonged to the Venus de Milo.
下周就去德州
Going out to Texas next week.
这个画廊的拥有者想让我 得到伪造的罪名
So this gallery owner's trying to get me on a forgery rap.
伪造罪?Moi?
Forgery?Moi?
我从不伪造 我克隆
I don't forge,I clone.
不管怎么样 如果我不能站起来的话 那就没有审讯了
Anyhow,the whole trial's redundant if I can't stand.
因此要表演一下
Hence the performance.
那你认为蒙德里安的故事怎么样?
So what do you think of this Mondrian scam?
Picasso之前 真是聪明
Pre-Picasso.Very cute.
自然 三个臭皮匠 你不可能愚弄Saatchi的宠物沙鼠
Total cobblers,of course.You wouldn't fool Saatchi's pet gerbil.
但是我认为你很厉害
But I thought you were good.
伪造品通常卖给那些富有的傻瓜
Forgeries are generally sold to wealthy idiots.
电影明星 日本渔民
Movie stars,Japanese fishing barons who never bother...
那些人从来不会为付账烦恼
to get them checked out.
但是你想用一个假冒的蒙德里安的作品去欺骗Meredith Gates
You want to flog a fake Mondrian to Meredith Gates...
一个蒙德里安作品主要的收集者
a leading Mondrian collector.
好的 你要什么?
Okay.What do you need?
一打意大利马毛刷子 大小是4-9号
A dozen Italian horsehair brushes,sizes 4 to 9.
有一定时间的再造帆布
Reconstituted canvas circa the period.
它能让我们在碳同位素测年法中达到 我们想要的时期
Not that that will get us around the carbon-dating.
是的 还要个原作
Yes,and an original.
得了吧 我们可以给你个出版物
Come on.We can get you a print.
我可以从书里面看到
I got pictures in books.
我需要去闻 去抚摸 去体验
I need to smell,caress,taste.
我需要一个真的蒙德里安在我身边
I need a real Mondrian sitting beside me.
毕竟 你们在说创造一副新画
After all,you're talking about originating a new piece.
这必须达到天衣无缝
This has to be perfect.
拿着它 冷静点
Hold on.Calm down.
麻烦一下 你能拿着它吧?
Can you hold on to that,please?
- 坐这儿 - 真是个混乱的地方
- Sit there. - That was a shambles.
把Gates小姐叫来 我要马上和她说话
Now get me Miss Gates.I need to speak with her at once.
什么?她在布里斯托尔
What?She's in Bristol.
那好,给她打电话
Well,get her on the phone.
一个人走进你的画廊然后从墙上拿起了你价值不菲的画
A man walks into your gallery and lifts a valuable painting off the wall.
为什么它没有被拴上?你们的激光保护呢?
Why wasn't it bolted down?Where's your laser protection?
据我所知花园都比你们的安全措施要好
I've seen garden centers with better security.
- 那儿有摄像机... - 如果停电怎么办?
- There's the cameras... - What's the downtime on the Mondrians?
这些画肯定是目标 怎么样 30秒钟?
Those paintings must be out of shot for,what,30 seconds?
只要20秒 它就不见了
Only 20,as it goes.
你是谁?
Who are you?
Debonair安全评估 就像你所意识到的
Debonair Security Assessments.As you may be aware...
最近有一些盗贼对于伦敦的画廊有所企图
there's been some recent theft attempts on London galleries.
艺术理事会要求我们检查你们有什么措施
The Arts Council asked us to check what measures you have in place...
为了保护这些艺术品
for insurance purposes.
我们有X光仪器 所有的画框都被做了记号
We have the X-ray machines,and all the frames are tagged.
你们不在帆布上做记号?
You don't tag the canvases?
不 Gates小姐的命令,没人可以去动油画
No.Miss Gates' instructions.No one tampers with the paintings.
听着 我想我最好和Gates小姐通下电话
Look,I think I'd better call Miss Gates.
好的 早点把她从布里斯托叫回来
Yeah,recall her from Bristol early.
她不会生气 是吗?
She won't be annoyed,will she?
只要告诉我一件事情
Just tell me one thing.
我们会做好的 不是吗?
We did all right,didn't we?
绅士们 我们Debonair的评估员对你们 的合作印象很深
Gents,it is not often that a Debonair assessor is impressed...
但是 从你们那里我们 知道了 谦卑 的真正含义
but this one just learnt the meaning of the word "humility."
这个就是你要的那个时期的画布
Here's the period canvas you asked for.
这个给你
This is for you.
它不能被仔细地去审查 但是他起码暂时可以去替换一下
It won't pass close scrutiny but it should do the job for the swap.
好的 我会把原画带回来的
Good.I'll be back with the original.
我要一张票
One,please.
之后将会有个小派对
Rest of my party are on the coach.
- 派对? - 蒙德里安的欣赏团体
- Party? - Mondrian Appreciation Society.
好的
All right.
我不知道是否简洁的构成 抑或是他的非对称性高雅...
I don't know if it's the economy of form or the elegance of his asymmetry...
他让我十分动心 是不是有点疯狂?
but he sets me alight.Is that crazy?
这是什么?
What's this?
这个是来访的纪录 如果你喜欢的话 可以签上名字
That is the visitors' record.Sign it,if you like.
那我马上我签了它
I'll sign it.I'll sign right now.
这个给你 免费的
To you,free.
谢谢 你人真不错
Thank you.That is so kind of you.
我们一直看护这些蒙德里安
We handle these Mondrians all the time.
这个是办公室的又一天 真的
It's another day at the office,really.
别说了
Stop it.
我喜欢那个疯狂的荷兰新塑料家
I like that crazy Dutch Neo-Plasticist.
你说的对
You're right.
他们有点晚了 你认为呢?
They're kind of late,don't you think?
- 厕所在哪里?我想小个便 - 这边请
- Where are the loos?I'm peeing my pants. - Right this way.
- 在你后面 一直走 - 谢谢你
- Behind you.Straight through. - Thanks.
再见
See you.
等下 你要去哪儿?
Wait.Where are you off to?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
你的小派对怎么样了?
What about your coach party?
将不一样了
Wouldn't be the same.
我更喜欢一对一
I like things a little more one-to-one.
知道我的意思了吗?再见
Know what I mean?Bye.
为了以后考虑 像这样运输 是个不错的点子
For future reference,it's a good idea when transporting a painting like this...
用个棉布包 没有研磨的
to use a muslin bag.Non-abrasive.
你要帮我重新布置这个地方 桌子在那儿 椅子排成一行
You gotta help me rearrange this place.Tables there.Chairs in a row.
蒙德里安喜欢秩序感 我也必须这样
Mondrian believed in order.So must I.
真的要这么做吗?艺术
It really does it for you,doesn't it?Art.
不是为你做吗?
Doesn't it for you?
听着 伙伴 我母亲有一幅画
Listen,mate.My mum had a painting.
叫 星期天的邮件
Got it out of The Mail on Sunday. Massive.
- 一群狗在玩斯诺克 - 刷子呢?
- A lot of dogs playing snooker. - Brushes?
- 这些应该浸泡在过醋 - 已经泡过了
- These need to be distressed in vinegar. - Already done.
这就是你要的颜料 高铅含量的
And here are the oils you asked for.High lead content as requested.
去掉净重 每管的厂家都不同
Got them off the Net.Different suppliers for each tube.
你要五罐沙丁鱼 为什么?
You asked for five tins of pilchards.Why?
这是沙滩的场景 所以我去了回布赖顿
It's a beach scene,so I took a trip to Brighton.
这是你要的海水
Here's your pot of seawater.
还有这个 我想他会在沙滩上绘画
And here,I thought if he was painting on a beach...
在画布上面应该会有沙砾进去
the sand would have gotten caught on the sticky canvas.
11天完成
In 11 days...
你们将拥有一副 蒙德里安的1902年的原画
an original Mondrian from 1902 will be in your possession.
它会 在短期之内 愚弄世界上最好的专家
It will,for a brief time,fool the greatest art experts in the world...
它同时也会废除毕加索 现代艺术之父的美称
and it will dethrone Picasso as the father of modern art.
或者它应该现在就停止 否则我们会去监狱呆上几年
Or it will be spotted immediately and we'll all go to prison for several years.
- 我可以拿走这包火柴吗? - 当然可以
- May I take these matches? - Yeah,sure.
嗨 对不起
Hi.Sorry.
我很高兴你打电话给我
I'm so glad you called.
对于那天的事情我深感抱歉 我有点草率
I'm sorry about the other day.I was a bit hasty.
你不要太介意
You can't be too careful.
告诉我 这幅画在Amersfoort找到的吗?
Tell me,was this piece uncovered in Amersfoort?
让我们先喝点东西吧
Let's get some drinks.
不是吧 Amersfoort
Come on.Amersfoort.
劳驾 我能来电酸果蔓汁吗?一杯Sea Breeze给这位女士
Excuse me.Could I have a cranberry juice and a Sea Breeze for the lady?
一个荷兰的中部城市 蒙德里安的出生地
A town in central Holland,Mondrian's birthplace.
对 如果还没公开的话就太好了
Yes,it would have been nice if it had been uncovered...
在蒙德里安的家乡 但是呢 并没有
in Mondrian's hometown.But alas,not.
你有照片吗?
Do you have a photo?
我身上什么都不带
No,I carry nothing with me.
但是我不想因为这一个发现 而感受太多爆炸性的意义
But I cannot stress the explosive significance of this find.
可我一直在想这一点呢
But I've been thinking about that.
它是不是来自西班牙的探险?
Could this be a piece from the Spanish expedition?
你为什么这么说?
Why do you say that?
拖住她 我们正在查找
Hang fire.We're on to it.
Albert
Albert.
1921年伟大的西班牙展览会
The Great Spanish Exhibition of 1921.
不,我在谈论蒙德里安的西班牙之行
No,I'm talking about Mondrian's trip to Spain.
- 当然 - 探险
- Of course. - Expedition.
我多糟糕的耳朵啊
What a deaf cretin.
快点 他就像个柠檬似的在那里
Hurry up.He's sitting there like a lemon.
坚持住
Hold on.
Hook先生 你让我摇摆不定
Mr.Hook,you're leaving me dangling.
你认为这幅画被蒙德里安和他最好的朋友Simon Maris
You think that this piece heralds from the trip Mondrian took to Spain...
在1901年带去了西班牙
with his best friend Simon Maris in 1901.
据你所知 没有记录
"As you know,no writing..."
或者画从那次旅行中留下
...or painting remains from that trip.
可能 但是 他或许见过了毕加索
"Possible,though,that he might have met Picasso."
你认为他可能在那见过了毕加索吗?
Do you think he may have met Picasso out there?
我知道
I knew it!
你在揭示在立体主义前面一个抽象的蒙德里安
You've uncovered an abstract Mondrian that predates Cubism.
我有一小幅画 它需要确认
I have a small painting that needs verification.
我希望一个专业的记者来帮助我
I would like an expert journalist on hand to assist.
整个世界将不得不深信不疑
The wider world will have to be convinced.
它将会这样 我能独家报道
And they will be.In an exclusive.
为什么是我?
Why me?
为什么找我这样的初出茅庐的人来写?
Why pick a fledgling writer?
你不是一个愤世嫉俗的人
You're not a cynic.
你一直很努力
You have no axe to grind.
你使我公开这个冒险
And you strike me as being open to adventure.
你需要等待 等到你能看到或者摸到它的时候
Just you wait.You wait until you can see it and touch it.
- 什么时候? - 很快
- When? - Very soon.
你真的相信我吗?
You do believe me,don't you?
事实上 是的
Actually,I do.
没人会比他更出色
Nobody does it better.
- 他这点让我感到沮丧 - 是的
- Makes me feel sad for the rest. - Yeah,right.
对不起 Stacie
Sorry,Stacie.
你早就知道Meredith Gates的兴趣了吧?
You already knew about Meredith Gates' interest,didn't you?
我有吗?
Did I?
我知道Pomeroy先生一直想买它
I know Mr.Pomeroy is keen to buy it.
他将今天去拜访Gates小姐 现在 事实上 他告诉我的
He's seeing Miss Gates today.Now,in fact.He told me.
是啊 他或许在找一个买卖的合伙人
Well,he may be looking for a buying partner.
他正在与一个蝎子作舞伴
He's dancing with a scorpion there.
我必须走了
I have to go.
你的帐单 先生
Your bill,sir.
我的朋友 在那个桌子会买单的
My friends are picking up the tab.
那么你要在我回来后去看看 Meredith Gates?
So you went to see Meredith Gates behind my back?
我想要做的就是使她上钩 你知道的
All I did was froth her up a bit,you know.
我告诉她我要用50万来买这画
I told her I was gonna buy the painting for 500,000.
你知道 只要压一个赌注在上面 她会激动不已
You know,just take a gamble on it.She got all agitated.
我告诉你 Mickey
I'm telling you,Mickey...
当你准备给Meredith看这幅画的时候
when we're ready to show Meredith this painting...
她肯定会很激动的
she's gonna be so jazzed about it...
她最少会出价50万
she's gonna snap it up for 500,000 minimum...
从我眼皮底下把画买走
just to swipe it from under my nose.
看来这个意见很不错
Seems this meeting has been all for the good.
确是如此
Yes,definitely.Very good.
虽然还有一个很小的问题
There is a teensy-weensy problem,though.
Meredith认为我在西肯塔基有着一家进出口公司
Meredith thinks I run an import-export company in West Ken.
她明天11点会带着她的决定来的
And she's coming over tomorrow at 11:00 with her decision.
早上好 我的毛茸茸的小伙伴
Good morning,my little furry friend.
老鼠
Rats.
- 早上好 Gates小姐 - 早上好
- Good morning,Miss Gates. - Morning.
你真决定为它支付5万?
Are you really going to pay 500,000 for it?
我的最高价格实际上是25万
My ceiling's actually 250,000...
但是我在寻找一个能匹配我的合伙人
but I'm looking for a partner who can match me.
你知道 如果你诚恳地话 它会值好几百万
You know,if this is genuine,it could be worth several million.
不管外貌如何 Hook先生不是一个富有的人
Despite appearances,Mr.Hook is not a wealthy man.
如果它的价值真的值几百万的话
And if it does turn out to be worth millions...
我认为他唯一权利就是从中有收获
I think it's only right that he gets a cut.
Hook只会得到我们给他的
Mr.Hook will only get what we give him.
如果他要更多 他可以烧掉他的50万
If he wants any more,he can burn up his 500,000...
用在法庭上和我对峙
chasing me through the courts.
好了 我们将一起去我的画廊看下画
Right.So,we will view the painting at my gallery together.
如果我满意的话 我会考虑和你五五分
If I am satisfied,then I will consider going 50-50 with you.
Gates小姐 你真是太慷慨了
That's incredibly generous,Miss Gates.
那么你愿意安排我和Hook先生的会面吗?
So you'll arrange this meeting with Mr.Hook?
当然 我还邀请了一个记者 Bea Watson小姐
Sure.I've also invited a journalist,Bea Watson.
我认为如果这件事是真的 我们应该扩大影响
I thought if this thing's genuine,we should bang the drum.
除非是好的消息
Only if it's good news.
再见
Bye.
她上钩了
Yes,we're on.
我们离要的赌注还很远
We are so far from the jackpot.
任何时候你想给我点鼓励的话 让自己放松点
Any time you wanna give me some encouragement,just feel free.
这不是一个俱乐部
This is not a club.
你不是在用四级诈骗赚取一个童子军的包
You're not earning a scouting badge for Grifting Grade 4.
我们在为了大笔的钱而让某人名誉扫地
We are taking a person down for a lot of money.
我们有这么多危险要跃过去
And we have so many hoops to jump through...
不仅仅是一幅我们从未见过的画
not least of which is a painting we haven't seen yet...
由一个我们不信任的人画的 我们也成了艺术品盗贼
painted by a man we can't trust.And we are also art thieves.
- 够酷 - Danny 这一点不酷
- Cool. - It is not cool,Danny!
我们不是骗子 我们是矿工
We're not crooks.We're miners.
我们挖掘人们的贪婪 而且这些人都是危险的人物
We mine people's greed.And these people can be dangerous.
我想说的就是 给我们现在的构成
All I'm saying is that given our current form...
我不准备喝香槟来庆祝
I'm not about to start letting off champagne corks.
那你不相信的话为什么去做?
Then why do it if you don't believe in it?
因为我们需要钱
Because we need the money.
- 那你要钱干什么? - 你会明白的
- What do you need the money for? - You'll see.
我会喜欢吗?
Will I like it?
快点 我们有很多工作要去做
Come on,we've got a lot of work to do.
这幅画将在一个星期之内完成
The painting will be ready in just one week.
- 等下 我看上去怎么样? - 很不错
- All right,how am I looking? - Beautiful.
好的 要不 来个好运之吻?
Okay,so how about a good-luck kiss?
走吧
Let's go.
Meredith在哪里?
Where's Meredith?
我希望你不介意我带我的教子与我一起
I hope you don't mind me bringing my godchildren along.
他们正在进行他们的6岁生日
They're on their way to a sixth birthday party.
主题是文艺复兴
The theme is Renaissance.
去玩吧
Off you go and play.
他们长得真是快 不是吗?
They grow up so fast,don't they?
厚颜无耻的小混蛋 不是吗?
Cheeky little fellows,aren't they?
画在哪里?
Where's the painting?
Hook先生在我们谈话的时候会带来的
Mr.Hook is bringing it even as we speak.
快点
Come on.
沙丁鱼!这跟沙丁鱼有什么关系?
Pilchards!What is this thing with pilchards?
- 喂喂 - 不错 你找到关键了
- Hello.- Good,you found the key.
- 画在哪里? - 碗橱的顶部 银色的箱子里面
- Where's the painting?- Silver case,top of the cupboard.
对不起
Excuse me.
到底发生了什么事情?
What the hell is going on?
Pomeroy先生的助手 哦 Hook先生
Mr.Pomeroy's assistant.Oh,Mr.Hook.
我找到了箱子 但是它被锁住了
I've got the case,but it's locked.
没有炸药的话我没有办法打开它
There's no way to open it without a detonator.
没问题 稍等
That's no problem.Hang on a minute.
喂喂
Hello.
我们需要打开那箱子的密码
We need a code to get into the case.
是吗?你应该为这件事高兴 我在这儿等你
Yeah?You can relax on that.I've got that right here.
- 发消息给我 - 一定会的
- Text it to me. - Absolutely.
好吧
Right.
Albert 我们快迟到了 你在哪儿?
Albert,we're running late.Where are you?
我们已经就位了 别为我们操心 好好干好你的工作吧
In position.Don't worry about us,just do your job,son.
好的
Right.
你并没有带来那一半钱吧?
You did bring your half?
是的 夫人 25万银行的支票
Yeah,ma'am.Banker's draft for 250,000...
就在这里
right here.
再给2分钟 要不我就走了
Two minutes,I'm leaving.
好了 我要走了 过来吧 我的小天使们
That's it.I'm leaving.Come along,my cherubs.
对不起
Sorry.
对不起让你们久等了
Sorry to have kept you good people waiting.
交通真是很糟糕
Traffic was awful.
是它吗?
Is this it?
- 兴奋吗? - 是的 打心眼里
- Excited? - Yes,indeed.
这个箱子需要安全密码只有我有
This case is security-coded and I have the code...
就在我的手机里面
here on my phone.
署名蒙德里安 1902年
Signed Piet Mondrian,1902.
这是他从未使用过的风格直到
It's in a style he wasn't supposed to employ until...
数年之后
Years later.
在画的表面上含有很多灰尘
There's quite a bit of dust embedded in the top layer.
画还闻起来有
Picture has a smell.
鱼 恶心 腐烂的味道
Fishy.Rank.Decay.
有着蒙德里安后期作品的诸多特点
Bears many of the hallmarks that Mondrian used later on...
但是有意思的是 我对这个有迟疑
but it's interesting.There's a hesitancy about it.
所有的艺术家都尝试着一些新的 或者他害怕的事物
Almost like an artist trying something very new and scaring himself.
我的天呐
My God.
好的 如果它不是赝品
Well,if it's not a fake...
那就是真的,我的天呐
then "My God," indeed.
这只是一个初步的评估 当然
This is only an initial assessment,of course...
但是它却是显现出诸多蒙德里安作品的特点
but it would appear that this work bears the traits of a Mondrian...
在二十世纪开始的时候画的
painted at the turn of the century.
但是 这副画画在了一块质地良好的帆布上
But this picture was painted on a fine-quality canvas.
蒙德里安不会把这么好的帆布 浪费在这样一个实验性的作品上
Mondrian wouldn't have wasted a top canvas on experimental work...
它明显不像是拿去卖的
that was unlikely to sell.
他或许已经搞定了
He may have done.
他是一个吝啬的而且小心翼翼的人
The man was meticulous and he was frugal.
他大多数的作品都画在纸板上面
Most of his work was done on cardboard.
可能这是一个委托
Perhaps it was a commission.
一个委托?
A commission?
当时没有人愿意花钱去买这样的东西
Nobody would have paid for something like this back then.
再怎么说 如果它是个委托的话 我们会有记录的
Anyway,if it was a commission,we'd have records.
显而易见 Hook先生 这个游戏结束了
It would seem,Mr.Hook,that the circus is over.
如果他被雇来画一些传统的东西
What if he was hired to paint something traditional...
他着手于一块好的帆布但是委托中途停止了
so he splashed out on a good canvas,but the commission fell through...
于是他又重新利用了?
so he reused it?
- 这块帆布 - 对 就是这样
- The canvas. - Yeah.
我喜欢听起来这样
I like the sound of that.
跟我来
Follow me.
如果你说的是对的话 Watson小姐 拿就应该有另一幅画
If what you say is correct,Miss Watson,then there should be another painting...
藏在这幅画的下面
hidden underneath here somewhere.
什么都没有
Nothing.
就像我所说的 你该烧毁了它
As far as I'm concerned,you can burn it.
等下 如果我调整下解析度
Wait.If I adjust the resolution...
一个下层图案
A pentimento!
一个隐藏在下面的风景画 看到了吗?
A hidden landscape underneath.You see?
当这个委托未能实现 蒙德里安肯定发怒了
When the commission fell through,Mondrian must have been furious.
他用激进的手法来发泄他的怒火
He vented his frustration in something radical.
一个与众不同的海滩
A beach scene like no other,ever.
Hook先生
Mr.Hook...
我现在就给你50万现金
I will give you 500,000 right now,in cash.
对不起 那我的另外一半呢?
Sorry.What about my half?
Hook先生 现金支付
In cash,Mr.Hook.
在拍卖会上我或许会得到5倍钱
I might get five times that at auction.
如果这是真的
If it's genuine.
你依然不这么认为?
You still don't think so?
先不说画 我被说服去冒这个风险
Put it this way.I'm persuaded to take a risk.
除非我有唯一的拥有权
But only if I have sole possession.
我有一张25万的银行支票
I've a banker's draft here for 250,000!
Hook先生 你愿意做这笔交易吗?
Mr.Hook,do we have a deal?
你不该这么大胆
Don't you dare.
成交
Deal.
我告诉你,我玩了个障眼法
I've played a blinder,I'm telling you.
即使当Meredith发现这幅画是一个伪造品
Even when Meredith discovers it's a fake...
她对此已经无能为力了
she's not gonna want to do anything about it.
她不可能在想让她的名字出现在所有的报纸之上
There's no way she'd want her name splashed all over the papers.
那么 去除小费和其他开销 我们面对的是
So,minus Tip's fee and other expenses,we're looking at...
每个人5万
50,000 each.
那我海景别墅的目标开始变得更近了
That dream beach-house of mine is starting to look a lot closer.
我不敢相信你还拥护那些坏运气 Mickey
I can't believe you went for all that bad karma shit,Mickey.
一个人会去创造他的好运的 伙计
A man creates his own luck in this world,son.
15万
150,000.
谢谢给了这么多 如果你不介意的话我还想再分一部分
Ta very much,but I'll take the lot,if you don't mind.
什么?
What?
现在我的一个朋友正在等着去打电话给警察
Right now a friend of mine is waiting to call the police.
他们会告诉警察一副蒙德里安的画 在Gates画廊被偷窃了
They will tell the cops a Mondrian has been stolen from the Gates Gallery.
他们会把你的名字给警察
They will give them your names.
警察会逮捕你 他们也会找到前面说到的画
The cops will arrest you.They will find said painting.
你将去监狱
You will go to prison.
还有 你的名字将会遍布国家的新闻媒体
And what is more,your identities will be blown by the national press.
这会使你在这个久经世故的社会中
That will make it very hard for you to pull off any more cons...
赢得更多的骗术
in sophisticated society.
但是 有一个拯救措施
But there is salvation.
分给我那一半 这个电话将不会发生
Give me the half mil,the call is never made.
你从不闭嘴吗 Tip?
Do you ever shut up,Tip?
你已经有这些最好的东西了
You've got all these fine things around you.
你已经叫嚣完了你的聪明的言论
You've got all your clever talk and all your yap.
但是你知道你是什么吗?你只是一个二传手
But you know what you are?You're just a tosser.
卡拉瓦乔是一个恶毒的女王
Caravaggio was a vicious queen.
米开朗基罗追赶过小男孩
Michelangelo shagged little boys.
培根是一个酒鬼
Bacon was an alcoholic.
高更娶了一个13岁的小女孩 欢迎来到艺术的世界
And Gauguin married a 13-year-old girl.Welcome to the art world.
就像你喜欢你的世界 Danny 我们就像穿着体面衣服的蟑螂
Just like your world,Danny.We are merely cockroaches with good tailors.
那么你的那位准备打电话给警察的朋友是谁 Tip?
So who is this friend of yours that's gonna call the cops then,Tip?
我觉得你不必要知道
I don't think you need to know.
放松
Easy.
你还要从Mickey身上学很多东西 他知道如何控制行为
You can learn a lot from Mickey.He knows how to behave.
我当然知道
I certainly do.
还要10秒钟 我认为
Ten seconds,I reckon.
10秒钟 会发生什么?
Ten seconds.Until what?
我早就叫他们来了
I called them earlier...
然后我想我只是听到一辆汽车 在外面停下来
and I think I just heard a car pull up outside.
- 3,2 ,1 - 这是什么?
- 3,2,1... - What is this?
D.S.Martins 欺诈组
D.S.Martins,Fraud Squad.
好的 请进 长官
Yes,come in,officer.
你记得我 是吗 Jones先生?
You remember me,don't you,Mr.Jones?
我们有得到一个你邻居的电话
We've had a call from a neighbor.
他说他看到你走在公园里面 Jones先生
He says he saw you walking in the park,Mr.Jones.
现在 我们的调查在医学悬而未决范围下
Now,what with our investigation under suspension on medical grounds...
我们觉得最好是突然拜访下然后来一个 小小的交谈
we felt it best to pop down here and have a little chat.
之后我们就走
We'll be off then.
再见 Jones先生 很高兴见到你
Bye-bye,Mr.Jones.Nice to see you.
这儿有不少钱 长官
Lot of money here,sir.
是的 这跟我们没有关系
Yes.Nothing to do with us.
- 你知道他会反咬一口 - 我很清楚他
- You knew he was gonna turn. - I was pretty sure.
- 我们可能会少了一份钱 - 我告诉你 飞的离太阳太近
- We could have lost the lot. - I told you,flying close to the sun.
但是Tip还是可以用那画来反咬我们一口
But Tip can still turn us in with that painting.
她在这儿干什么?
What's she doing here?
太聪明了 还给我
Very clever.Give them back.
Danny 她就是叫警察的人
Danny,this is the person who calls the cops...
然后告诉他们 哪儿可以找到被盗的蒙德里安的作品
and tells them where to find a stolen Mondrian.
伪造者常常用他们的学生来 保护他们的伪造品
Forgers often use students to fence their forgeries.
她是个骗子吗?
She's a grifter?
我是个严谨的艺术专栏作家 谢谢
I'm a serious arts writer,thank you.
你在哪儿见到Tip的?
Where did you meet Tip?
在大学里 那儿他们一般都招新成员
At college.That's where they usually recruit.
在大学的每一个人都知道Tip
Everyone at college knew Tip.
当你访问他之后 Tip打电话给我
After you visited him,Tip called me...
我们就选择这种方法
and we sort of came up with this.
太好了 那现在发生了什么?
Great.So what happens now?
为什么你们不拿着你们的钱
How about you keep your money...
而我拿走蒙德里安的画
and I'll hang on to the Mondrian.
不 蒙德里安的画必须要归还 这是我们做事的原则
No,the Mondrian has to go back.That's the way we work.
很好 但是它不是我做事的原则
Well,it's not the way I work.
很好 如果你可以得到它的话
Well,if you can live with that...
那你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
- 怎么样了 伙计们? - 还不坏
- How'd it go,boys? - Not bad.
不会吧!你还好吗?
Don't!You all right?
别担心 是我的错误 我见到你车子后就想走快一点
Don't worry,it was my fault.I stepped out in front of you.
我甚至没看到你
I didn't even see you.
能不能扶我一下 我这样看上去很笨拙
Can't bend me leg.I landed awkward.
我从未遇到过这种事情
It never happened to me before.
看阿 我可以动了 别担心 美女 我很快就好
Look at that,I can move it.Don't worry,love,I'll be fine.
这又是我们的一个漂亮的工作
Yeah,it was nice working the flop again.
那么你怎么知道她在撒谎?
So how did you know she was lying?
在鸡尾酒吧里面
At the cocktail bar.
你真的相信我 不是吗?
You do believe me,don't you?
她透露了她知道
She revealed a tell.
事实上 我相信
Actually,I do.
我仔细检查了
I double-checked it.
兴奋吗?
Excited?
她的手割过自己的喉咙 一个典型的知情者
The throat-slash.A classic tell.
是的 打心底里
Yes,indeed.
通常所表现的诸多于罪恶相关联的感情
Usually associated with feelings of guilt.
所以你更加确定了她会出卖我们
So you double-guessed the double-cross.
我只是想采取一些保险措施
I just took out some insurance.
好吧 吸取些经验
Well,take away the expenses...
我们始终还是拿到了30万在皮箱里
we've still got over 300,000 in the pot.
20万,还有10万将有其他用处
200,000.100,000 is going somewhere else.
哪儿?
Where?
不 不行 你不能这么做
No,no way.You can't.
对不起 如果我们不这么做 这个人会因为我们失去一切的
I'm sorry.But if we don't,this man loses everything because of us.
那也会给我们永久带来坏运气
And that'll jinx us forever.
你不会相信这些这些废话吧 Ash 是吗?
You don't believe all this crap,do you,Ash?
我们必须去做了 Danny
We gotta do it,Danny.
- Stace? - 让他去吧 Danny
- Stace? - Let it go,Danny.
听着10万给Naveen做一些补偿
Look,100,000 pays Naveen back and makes amends.
我们不是盗贼 Danny
Danny,we're not thieves.
快点 Danny
Danny,come on.
这是我的诈骗 好吗?
This was my grift,all right?
你应该告诉我一下
You should've told me.
你说的对 对不起
You're right.I'm sorry.
好的 Danny 你决定去做吧
Okay,Danny,you decide what happens next.
拿着 Danny
Danny,come on.
不管做什么样的决定 只要相信
Only please make sure whatever decision you make...
你可以以此为生
you can live with.
因为做过的事情已经过去
Because what's done is done.
如你们所知,接手者已经进来了
As you know,the receivers are in.
对不起 各位
...so sorry,everyone.
真是废话,这只是钱 不是吗?
Bollocks.It's only money,isn't it?
不管么说 我又有了个新的好主意
Anyway,I've got a great new idea.
好了 清理下头绪 想象下
Right,clear your minds,picture this:
我们有半头奶牛 和一匹设得兰小马
We've got half of a cow,a small Shetland pony...
- 还有一些防腐剂... - 以后再说吧
- and some embalming... - Tell me later.
我很高兴这些无聊的事情被解决了 快点 我请客了
I'm glad this silly matter is settled.Come on,I'm buying.My round.
那封Rachel的律师来的信
That envelope from Rachel's lawyer.
你从没有打开过吗?
Did you ever open it?
我决定还清她的帐
Yeah.I've decided to pay her off.
- 坏运又来了吗? - 嗯...
- Jinx lifted? - Well...